devatube.com 2013-12-01

# 

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR TUBEJOY.COM**

This Privacy Policy statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data that is received or gathered regarding Members, visitors and Users of Tubejoy.com (hereafter the “Site”) or the services provided by this Site.

  CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR USE OF THIS SITE AND ITS SERVICES YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

  IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT USE THIS SITE OR THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY THIS SITE.

    **1\. MEMBER, VISITOR OR USER INFORMATION**

  If you visit this Site, we will collect and store in our database only the following non-personally identifying information from you; the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site.

  We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our Site, to help us make our site more useful to visitors, and to measure the amount of traffic generated through our affiliate network with whom this information may be shared.

  The only personally-identifying information we collect and store about you is the information you, voluntarily choose to provide to us, such as your Username, e-mail address, address, zip code, etc. In addition, we may ask you to voluntarily provide us with personal information when you become a Member for billing and shipping purposes.

  When a Member, visitor or User of this Site requests web pages from the Site’s server or clicks on banners or other hypertext links, the Site may automatically collect some information or data about the Member, visitor or User, including the IP address from which the Site is being accessed, the pages or links that were requested, the special preferences or requests of the Member, visitor or User and cookie information received from the computer of the Member, visitor or User; all that information and data may be collected by the Site and included in its database.

  If a Member, visitor or User sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and include that information in its database.

  **2\. COOKIES**

Tubejoy.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information to make your online experience easier and more personalized. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Most major Web browsers are set up so that they will initially accept cookies, but you may modify your computers preferences to issue you an alert when a cookie is downloaded, or to disable the ability of third parties to download a cookie to you. If you choose to reject all cookies, there are areas of this Site and other websites that may not function properly.

  You may obtain further information about “cookies” and how they function at: http://www.cookiecentral.com

  **3\. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND DISCLAIMER**

  By the use of the Site or its services, the Member, visitor or User expressly agrees that the Site may use any information that it gathers or collects about the Member, visitor or User including personal information that has been provided by the Member, visitor or User for technical, administration, research and development, customer administration, age verification, marketing, promotional and advertising use and for the transmission of email communications, the sending of products or the fulfilling of any terms and conditions; and furthermore that the Site may disclose or provide such personal information to its affiliates, agents and service providers that provide goods and services, for purposes of providing such goods and services.

  The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a Member, visitor or User may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the Site. This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites, and those third-party websites may have different privacy policies than this Site. Whenever applicable, each Member, visitor or User should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site.

  All Members, visitors and Users of this Site should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as non-confidential, and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any Member, visitor or User is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

By your acts of signing up as a subscriber to the Site, accepting the Terms and Conditions of the Site and affirmatively consenting to accept emails from this Site, you are agreeing to all of the following: (1) that Site has your permission to collect your email address and all personal information you supply relating to that email address; (2) that Site has your permission to disclose and transfer your email address and all other personal information you supply to its affiliates, agents or service providers that provide goods and services in accordance with the Terms and Conditions of Tubejoy.com .

  **4\. “OPT-OUT” – REVOCATION OF CONSENT PROCEDURE**

  The Site also offers all Members and Users a procedure for “Opting-Out” if the Member or User subsequently chooses to revoke or withdraw any consent to receive Offers by sending an e-mail to [cs@tubejoy.com](mailto:cs@tubejoy.com) clearly stating that the Member or User has revoked or withdrawn consent to receive any future Offers.

  **5\. DISCLOSURE**

  Tubejoy.com will not disclose or use any of your personally identifiable information except to the extent set forth in this Privacy Policy, or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to enforce any of our rights and terms and conditions or identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Tubejoy.com [Terms and Conditions](http://in.cybererotica.com/terms/terms_ar.html?site=tubejoy.com) .

    **6\. REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

  This Site reserves the right, in its sole and absolute discretion, to revise, amend, modify or revoke this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. Changes to this Policy will be effective by posting revisions on the Site. This Privacy Policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
